vkool.com 2013-12-06

# Privacy Policy

With **Vkool** , you can benefit from our services in different ways:

  * To search for information
  * To share useful information
  * To communicate with other visitors and users
  * To create new content

Also, when sharing information with [Vkool](http://vkool.com/), users can receive better services in:

  * Getting more relevant search results and ads,
  * Connecting and sharing with other visitors, customers fast and easier.
  * Using our services, you will be clear the ways we are using information that your privacy is confidentially protected.

## Information gathered by Vkool

In order to provide all of the users with better services, _Vkool_ collect information from basic stuff like which language our visitors or customers use to more complex things like the people who matter most to our users on the Internet or which ads are most useful for the visitors and customers.

Information [Vkool](http://vkool.com/) collect is from the one our visitors and customers share with us and from the one we get from our visitors and customers use of our services.

## How Vkool use information

From most of our products and services, Vkool uses the information to provide, maintain, update, protect as well as develop new ones. With this information, _Vkool_ offers visitors and customers with tailored content such as more available relevant search results and ads.

**Vkool** also take the information gathered from cookies as well as other technologies, such as pixel tags, to enhance the experience of visitors and customers as well as the overall quality of all our products and services. Before using any information for the purpose other than those which are set out in the Privacy Policy, the site [Vkool.com](http://vkool.com/) will surely ask visitors and users for their consent.

### Accessing and updating user’s personal information

Our company of _Vkool.com_ respects visitors and users’ privacy and permits them to control the treatment of their personal information. When visitors and users are required to submit their personal information to use or access our site or our service, they must complete the registration process by submitting the information requested on the form. Then, our visitors and users must agree to the terms provided in our company’s Privacy Policy regarding the use of the information they provide. Whenever using products or services in Vkool, we will provide visitors and users with access to their personal information. Or in case their information is not correct, _Vkool_ will manage to show them suitable ways to update it as soon as possible or even to delete it – unless Vkool must keep the information for legitimate business or for legal purposes. Visitors and users will have to verify their identity when updating their personal information before we act on their request.

We must remind visitors and users with requests that are considered to be unreasonably repetitive, risk the privacy of the other users, require disproportionate technical effort, or would be impractical (for example, requests referring the information residing on the backup tapes) may be rejected.

Where we can do freely provide the information access as well as correction, except where it requires a disproportionate effort. **Vkool.com** aims to maintain the products and services in a manner that help protect all the information from accidental and malicious destruction.

## Information Vkool share

Unless one of the circumstances apply: with the users’ consent, with domain administrators and for external processing, [Vkool](http://vkool.com/) assures to not share users’ personal information with individuals, companies, as well as organizations outside of our company. Based on our instructions, in compliance with Vkool’s Privacy Policy as well as any other appropriate confidentiality and also security measures, we provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us.

### Application

This Privacy Policy of _Vkool_ applies to the products and services that offered by our company and its affiliates, containing products and services provided on other sites, but excludes products or services that do not incorporate within our Privacy Policy.

The Privacy Policy on **Vkool** does not apply to products and services that are provided by other individuals or companies, including sites or products that may be seen by visitors and users in search results or other web sites linked from our products and services. Vkool’s Privacy Policy will not contain the information practices from other organizations and companies who advertise our products and services.

#### Contact

Please write to us by post to our postal address or by email if you have any further questions about our Privacy Policy as well as how we treat your personal information.
